▼ Resurrection Remix Nougat Ver 5.8.3 Changelog


 ▼ 05/07/2017


 ▪ project build/
 ▪ 2c4ef41 Add support to Dolby Atmos  to charge build
 ▪ a6128b7 Add support to Dobly atmos to charge build
 ▪ f44db34 Fix v4a
 ▪ 4bbda9e fix v4a build
 ▪ 24d572a test v4a to build

 ▪ project device/motorola/athene/
 ▪ cc3fee1 athene: lcd_density to 400

 ▪ project frameworks/base/

 ▪ project hardware/qcom/audio-caf/msm8937/
 ▪ 99617f9 Configs: remove audio sink buffer size property
 ▪ a9f2c00 hal: fix kw issue in hal
 ▪ 6191804 hal: remove redundant logs from utils.c
 ▪ 905d1d8 audiod: Skip enumerating non-ADSP sound cards

 ▪ project hardware/qcom/display-caf/msm8937/
 ▪ b7a3010 display: Add color metadata definition
 ▪ 26cd504 display: Add color metadata definition
 ▪ eb49512 sdm: Use ColorMetadata in SDM
 ▪ 37d5aff display: Add support for Rec.2020
 ▪ b6a2bfb sdm: Use safe mode on External display on low end device
 ▪ 9c64210 HWC: Set skip to layers with Non Integral Source Crop
 ▪ 93afadf sdm: skip null commit on command mode panels
 ▪ 2428bc4 libmemtrack: Fix integer overflow in kgsl function

 ▪ project hardware/qcom/media-caf/msm8937/
 ▪ de0c52e media: libOmxSw encoders require prop headers :(
 ▪ fcd1cfd mm-video-v4l2: serialize FTB's for dropped frames
 ▪ 057d1c7 mm-video-v4l2: vidc: venc: Free buffer FDs and handles
 ▪ a5da2d3 mm-video-v4l2: vdec: Support for HEVCMain10HDR10 profile
 ▪ 76dd49f mm-video-v4l2: Update max level for h264 decoder to 5.1
 ▪ 46aa731 mm-video-v4l2: venc: Disable Pframes incase of resolution 5k/6k
 ▪ 5dc8e7e mm-video-v4l2: Reset drv_ctx o/p buffer requirements in loaded state
 ▪ 0a4ad7e mm-video-v4l2: vdec: Convert maximum display luminance in cd/m2
 ▪ 9e702ea mm-video-v4l2: vdec:Metadata for HDR and ColorAspects
 ▪ 6076eb6 mm-video-v4l2: vdec: Support for HDR Info extension

 ▪ project packages/apps/Settings/
 ▪ 172e107 add support to v4a
 ▪ 7216057 add string v4a
 ▪ 11f2586 add          ic_xd_eq to v4a
 ▪ 47ca431 add          ic_xd_eq_alpha to v4a
 ▪ 64d80a9 add          ic_xd_eq_alpha to v4a
 ▪ b45f0ce add          ic_xd_eq_alpha to v4a
 ▪ dc46788 add          ic_xd_eq_alpha to v4a
 ▪ 8165007 add          ic_xd_eq_alpha to v4a
 ▪ 372d14f Add missing string

 ▪ project packages/services/OmniJaws/

 ▪ project vendor/cm/
 ▪ 8f7fb73 add Dobly Atmos
 ▪ 6c5ced0 add dolby atmos
 ▪ 47c3405 Add files via upload
 ▪ dfd9fe3 test v4a to build

 ▪ project vendor/motorola/
 ▪ 5f8b3e6 addison: Display blobs update
 ▪ 12285bf addison: Drop unneeded blobs
 ▪ 17d357d addison: Switch to OSS GPS
 ▪ 3a43b3d victara: Add libtqi-perfd-client.so

 ▼ 05/06/2017


 ▪ project frameworks/base/
 ▪ 948bba9 base: SystemUI: use content observer for recent grid config
 ▪ 73dbc18 base:refactor recents code to switch between recents
 ▪ b0f2122 [1/2] base: featureize ro.recents.grid
 ▪ 319c5f7 Update OmniSwitch string
 ▪ 9733626 OmniJawsClient : Move to framework
 ▪ e2192bc SysUI : Use a different approach to Make perf profile tile invisible
 ▪ 7805dad base: SystemUI: add dedicated TextView for OmniJaws error marker
 ▪ 9bdaacf base: SystemUI: dont show OmniJaws error that prominent

 ▪ project packages/apps/Dialer/

 ▪ project packages/apps/ResurrectionStats/
 ▪ 20ea10d ROMStats: modify for ResurrectionRemix

 ▪ project packages/apps/Settings/
 ▪ 048aad9 Refactor Recents Category
 ▪ d55ce18 Settings:featurize ro.recents.grid [2/2]
 ▪ c415aa0 Mantainers: Delete WinKarbik from ido mantainer (#784)

 ▪ project packages/services/OmniJaws/

 ▼ 05/05/2017


 ▪ project frameworks/base/

 ▪ project packages/apps/Dialer/

 ▪ project packages/apps/OmniSwitch/

 ▪ project packages/apps/Settings/
 ▪ 34a8e66 Change codename of K3 Note (#783)

 ▪ project packages/services/OmniJaws/

 ▪ project system/bt/
 ▪ 0ebf465 Do not include the trailing NULL from the C-String in the SDP service name

 ▼ 05/04/2017


 ▪ project bootable/recovery/
 ▪ 616bf9a recovery: Fix event system

 ▪ project frameworks/base/
 ▪ ed3936e Make Scrolling for TaskManager list a lot easier
 ▪ 03a9a2e Base:Dont do anything on weather errors for header & keyguard

 ▪ project kernel/motorola/msm8226/
 ▪ eabaaf5 netlink: Fix dump skb leak/double free
 ▪ 742bd0e msm: crypto: set CLR_CNTXT bit for crypto operations
 ▪ de9679e qseecom: check buffer size when loading firmware images
 ▪ 5a4f8bd ASoC: msm: qdsp6v2: Fix out-of-bounds access in put functions
 ▪ bf35e60 tcp: do not lock listener to process SYN packets
 ▪ 750f6a0 input: synaptics_dsx: protect tmpbuf allocation.
 ▪ ae466fb tmpfs: clear S_ISGID when setting posix ACLs
 ▪ 1ea2480 BACKPORT: posix_acl: Clear SGID bit when setting file permissions

 ▪ project packages/apps/Dialer/

 ▪ project packages/apps/Jelly/
 ▪ 2006774 Jelly: no need of using srcCompat for imageviews

 ▪ project packages/apps/OmniSwitch/

 ▪ project packages/apps/Settings/
 ▪ 008a015 Update resurrection_device_maintainers_strings.xml (#782)
 ▪ 33f769f Add device_maintainers_fragment for device thea (#780)
 ▪ 3e9cabc Add Device Maintainer for motorola moto g2 LTE (#781)

 ▪ project packages/services/OmniJaws/

 ▼ 05/03/2017


 ▪ project frameworks/base/
 ▪ e67fe65 KeyguardStatusBar: Add missing TouchAnimation for hiding statusbar
 ▪ 640db94 Base: Make sure keyguard and header handle weather errors as well
 ▪ d9c5ba7 base: SystemUI: dont hide navbar for screenshot crop
 ▪ 9fa52a5 base: SystemUI: qs: location tile quickbar press is just toggle
 ▪ 3db7979 base: SystemUI: dont hide weather forcast data on errors
 ▪ 4c60572 base: SystemUI: use new OmniJaws error broadcasts
 ▪ ad493bf Fix keyguard is black background while screen turning off/on quickly
 ▪ 41d90ba Reboot/Recovery QS Tile: Use vectorized icons

 ▪ project kernel/motorola/msm8226/
 ▪ 1a18e02 fs/proc/array.c: make safe access to group_leader
 ▪ f29e875 ALSA: info: Check for integer overflow in snd_info_entry_write()
 ▪ ff57117 perf: don't leave group_entry on sibling list (use-after-free)
 ▪ 9a56042 xfrm_user: validate XFRM_MSG_NEWAE incoming ESN size harder
 ▪ 176e3d5 xfrm_user: validate XFRM_MSG_NEWAE XFRMA_REPLAY_ESN_VAL replay_window
 ▪ 37308e4 input: touchscreen: gt9xx: fix memory corruption in Goodix driver
 ▪ 8304341 soc: qcom: scm: add check to avoid buffer overflow
 ▪ 49b3d1d ASoC: soc: prevent risk of buffer overflow
 ▪ 41cc25c ASoC: msm: qdsp6v2: return error when copy from userspace fails
 ▪ 81c5e81 ASoC: msm: qdsp6v2: Add range checking in msm_dai_q6_set_channel_map
 ▪ eb958e7 trace: resolve stack corruption due to string copy
 ▪ e4b58a8 ASoC: wcd9320: Fix out of bounds for mad input value
 ▪ 02ab642 slim-msm: Synchronize SSR callbacks
 ▪ 6084099 crypto: msm: check length before copying to buf in _debug_stats_read
 ▪ 3f70bb8 prima: Trim operation classes to max supported in change station
 ▪ 2ea1026 perf: Tighten (and fix) the grouping condition

 ▪ project packages/apps/Jelly/
 ▪ 9be745e Jelly: fix InflateException on builds compiled with aosp build system
 ▪ b01a7b8 Jelly: handle rotation and multiwindow changes

 ▪ project packages/apps/Settings/
 ▪ a2cd85e update a string

 ▪ project packages/services/OmniJaws/
 ▪ aa857b5 OmniJaws: come here all you hidden bugs into the bright light
 ▪ a169929 OmniJaws: weather widget fixes
 ▪ a9b5863 OmniJaws: add weather widget
 ▪ d106dcd OmniJaws: add error broadcast

 ▪ project vendor/motorola/
 ▪ 9b10207 victara: Hexedit libqc-opt.so for N
 ▪ 35319b9 victara: Switch to using libqc-opt

 ▼ 05/02/2017


 ▪ project android/
 ▪ 7c6e872 manifests: 7.1.2_r2-> r8
 ▪ 16e5022 android: nuke browser, welcome jelly
 ▪ 8ead0d4 Manifest : Stop syncing blank intel sensor repo.
 ▪ 1aaf24e manifest: Track our external/libchrome

 ▪ project bionic/
 ▪ 22d6b5b libc: ARM: Add 32-bit Kryo memcpy
 ▪ 45a3987 libc: use Cortex-A7/A53 memset on Kryo
 ▪ ba97f82 Add kryo support.

 ▪ project bootable/recovery/
 ▪ 8011e66 recovery: Fix UI freezing

 ▪ project build/
 ▪ fab5d1d Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into nougat
 ▪ e6c0264 Revert "We want Browser"

 ▪ project external/boringssl/
 ▪ 8f156df Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into cm-14.1

 ▪ project frameworks/av/
 ▪ 24697a3 Merge branch 'cm-14.1' of https://github.com/LineageOS/android_frameworks_av into nougat
 ▪ 16dcaaa Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into cm-14.1

 ▪ project frameworks/base/
 ▪ 0501270 Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into nougat
 ▪ e8d78b4 fix anr when concurrent request provider
 ▪ d0d7aee Ensure that the decor view is attached to window.
 ▪ 119e0d3 Bad token of activity when do the launch work at the app process side.
 ▪ 0555835 Query geo description in worker thread to prevent ANR
 ▪ a87340f remove duplicated incorrectly code in ProcessRecord
 ▪ 3f19033 fix foreground process will be mistakenly killed when it uses content provider.
 ▪ 1e33d08 Restart persistent process if start timeout.
 ▪ 88fd7c1 fix system_server crash issue caused by fd leak.
 ▪ 2f5069e Compass qs tile: Fix icon in edit mode

 ▪ project frameworks/native/
 ▪ c544fcc Merge branch 'cm-14.1' of https://github.com/LineageOS/android_frameworks_native into nougat
 ▪ b8fb318 Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into cm-14.1

 ▪ project kernel/motorola/msm8226/
 ▪ f033a00 net: avoid signed overflows for SO_{SND|RCV}BUFFORCE
 ▪ 4e441ac Fix "Add PR_{GET,SET}_NO_NEW_PRIVS to prevent execve from granting privs"

 ▪ project packages/apps/DUI/
 ▪ aba99d5 Fix Fling swipe up gesture being hard to trigger

 ▪ project packages/apps/Dialer/
 ▪ b239b70 Dialer: InCallUI: Enable Sustained Performance Mode We should make sure that thermals are stable during active calls, so we should enable Sustained Performance Mode for the InCallActivity.

 ▪ project packages/apps/Messaging/
 ▪ 9ea833a Merge branch 'cm-14.1' of https://github.com/LineageOS/android_packages_apps_messaging into nougat

 ▪ project packages/apps/Settings/
 ▪ 2c2376a Change username of Github from PixlernBlitz to PainKiller3 (#776)
 ▪ 38863c0 Fix typo in resurrection_device_maintainers.xml (#775)
 ▪ e6d2f89 Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into nougat
 ▪ f69dd8c Revert "Settings: Lost cached BT devices in found devices list"
 ▪ 226f681 Settings[Wifi]: fix the input invalid length for WEP encryption.
 ▪ 20f7649 Settings: Fix internal storage summary for non-emulated storage
 ▪ a8ca4b4 Add v521 device and maintainer  (#774)
 ▪ 9283d7e Add Galaxy Grand Prime As Official. (#773)

 ▪ project system/bt/
 ▪ 85d4e42 Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into cm-14.1

 ▪ project system/core/
 ▪ 259efc1 Merge branch 'cm-14.1' of https://github.com/LineageOS/android_system_core into nougat
 ▪ d7cbf4b Merge tag 'android-7.1.2_r8' into cm-14.1

 ▪ project vendor/cm/
 ▪ 137c340 cm: nuke browser, welcome jelly
 ▪ b43a798 cm: Remove obsolete and unused overlays and configs

 ▪ project vendor/motorola/
 ▪ 43d0c43 shamu: update blobs from N6F27C factory image
